{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete Patio Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40878/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40878,"taskName":"Concrete Patios, Walks \u0026 Steps- Install","taskDescription":"Install Concrete Patios, Walks and Steps","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete Patio Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":2501,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"concrete sidewalk install walkway patio","textMessagingName":"Inst Concrete Flat","rolloverLongDesc":"Used for walks, sidewalks, patios, porches and steps. Does not require extensive vertical forms. Appropriate when building or replacing old mostly flat concrete structures.","rolloverShortDesc":"Build forms, pour concrete, finish flat concrete","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Concrete Patios, Walks and Steps. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated concrete patio contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Concrete Patio Installation Contractors \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Concrete Patio, Steps, Stairs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Concrete Patios, Walks \u0026 Steps Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Concrete Patios, Walks \u0026 Steps - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Patio Project","urlName":"Concrete-Patio-Steps-Walks","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Patio Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Patio, Steps","searchKeywords":"concrete,sidewalk,install,walkway,patio,steps","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1433,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40878/":{"taskOID":40878,"originalTaskOID":40878,"setID":1433,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7029,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which concrete surfaces do you want to have installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10452,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10453,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10454,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7030,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of concrete project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10455,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replacement of existing concrete","answerDisplayText":"Replacement of existing concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10456,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New concrete for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New concrete for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10457,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New construction of home","answerDisplayText":"New construction of home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7031,"questionDisplayText":"Special applications/finishes","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special concrete applications or finishes you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10458,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Smooth trowel finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth trowel finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10459,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","answerDisplayText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10460,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10461,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cover electrical or radiant heat pipes","answerDisplayText":"Cover electrical or radiant heat pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10462,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stamped to look like stone, brick or tile","answerDisplayText":"Stamped to look like stone, brick or tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10463,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cover irrigation pipes, drains, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Cover irrigation pipes, drains, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10464,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7029,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which concrete surfaces do you want to have installed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10452,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10453,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10454,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10452,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10453,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10454,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7030,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of concrete project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10455,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replacement of existing concrete","answerDisplayText":"Replacement of existing concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10456,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New concrete for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New concrete for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10457,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New construction of home","answerDisplayText":"New construction of home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10455,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replacement of existing concrete","answerDisplayText":"Replacement of existing concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10456,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New concrete for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New concrete for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10457,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New construction of home","answerDisplayText":"New construction of home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7031,"questionDisplayText":"Special applications/finishes","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special concrete applications or finishes you are interested in:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10458,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Smooth trowel finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth trowel finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10459,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","answerDisplayText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10460,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10461,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cover electrical or radiant heat pipes","answerDisplayText":"Cover electrical or radiant heat pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10462,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stamped to look like stone, brick or tile","answerDisplayText":"Stamped to look like stone, brick or tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10463,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cover irrigation pipes, drains, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Cover irrigation pipes, drains, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10464,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10458,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Smooth trowel finish","answerDisplayText":"Smooth trowel finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10459,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","answerDisplayText":"Special color, stain, or other additive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10460,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","answerDisplayText":"Brush textured finish (slip-resistant)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10461,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cover electrical or radiant heat pipes","answerDisplayText":"Cover electrical or radiant heat pipes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10462,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stamped to look like stone, brick or tile","answerDisplayText":"Stamped to look like stone, brick or tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10463,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cover irrigation pipes, drains, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Cover irrigation pipes, drains, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10464,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}